Here I would like to show how the coefficients are retrieved in
这里我将要展示如何
your multiple in your aggression model using the matrix that you see here.
在多重线性回归模型中使用这里的矩阵检索系数
So here was the output that we received from
这是上节课视频中涉及的
the multiple lineal regression model that you saw in the last screen cast.
多重线性回归模型得到的输出
You can see that the coefficients are right here.
你可以看到系数在这里
These four values next to the intercept,
这里有四个值 截距
the number bathrooms, the number of bedrooms and the area.
卫生间数量 卧室数量和面积
We're going to show how do you get
我们将要展示你如何
these four things using just this data from the matrix up here.
使用这上面矩阵中的数据得到这四个值
First let's create an X matrix which will
首先创建 X 矩阵
just contain the portions that we saw in the output here.
其中只包含我们这里看到的输出部分
So we'll need one for the intercept,
所以我们需要一个表示截距
one for the bathrooms, one for the bedrooms and one for the area.
一个表示卫生间 一个表示卧室 一个表示面积
And actually we could just pull this part right here.
实际上我们只要把这部分拖放到这里
I'm going to call that our x matrix and y will then be just our response.
然后我们称之为 X 矩阵和 y 之后作为我们的反应变量
So, it will be only the price is the thing that we're trying to predict.
所以这里我们只需要预测价格
The closed form solution you can see up here.
这里可以看到闭合解
So, it says we get the estimates of our coefficient by taking
这样可以说 我们通过得到 X 估算系数
x and then this thing's called a transpose and then we multiply that by X.
这称为转置矩阵 然后乘以 X
We take the inverse and then we multiply that by
通过求逆运算 我们再乘以
the X transpose again and then by our response vector Y.
X 转置矩阵 然后乘以反应矢量 Y
So this is what we want to do and we'll obtain the coefficients that we get here.
这就是我们想要完成的 这里得到了我们想要的系数
In matrix multiplication, you don't multiply the same way you do with
在矩阵乘法中 你不需要采用纯量乘法的相同方式
scalars you're going to multiply using the dot product.
不能使用数量积相乘
Let's do a quick numPy search and see how we can get the transpose,
我们进行 numPy 快速搜索 观察如何利用转置矩阵
the inverses and the dot products to be able to calculate this.
求逆运算和数量积计算得到
So, here we can see that we have matrix transposing using this transpose and numPy.
这里我们可以看到 使用这个转置和 numPy 对矩阵进行变换
So, numPy and then transpose the matrix.
这样进行 numPy 然后对矩阵转置
And then the other things that we want,
然后另外我们还想做
the dot product and we can see that the documentation is available here.
即数量积 我们可以看到这里获取的文档
So numPy dot and then the last thing we want to do is invert.
所以 numPy 点 然后最后进行可逆运算
Great. And it looks like that's available with a numPy within a linear algebra portion.
非常棒 这样看起来可以在线性代数部分中可以用于 numPy
And then there's an inverse.
其次这是个倒数
So let's go ahead and try to use these.
然后我们继续使用这些
So, again, our formula looks like this right here.
我们的公式像是这里所示
So, we're going to take x transpose times X which will be a dot product of
我们对 X 转换 乘以这两个的数量积 X
these two things and then we want to invert that and then
然后进行可逆运算
dot product with the transpose and then dot product with the response.
再对转置矩阵进行数量积运算 对反应进行数量积运算
And that should give us the estimates for our coefficients.
这应该得出对系数的估算
So that should give us the transpose.
这样我们得到转置矩阵
And then we want to multiply that by X,
然后我们将之乘以 X
which is the dot product,
即数量积
and then we want to multiply that by so dot product that with X transpose again.
然后再次这样相乘 数量积乘以 X 转置矩阵
And then we want a final dot product with the response.
然后得到反应的最终数量积
We have X transpose rate,
我们得到 X 转置率
so x transpose X but then we need to invert this whole portion which we see up here.
x 转置为 X 然后需要对整个这一部分求倒数
So we need to use that linear algebra portion there.
我们需要使用这里的线性代数部分
So, in here I'm going to say np.linalg and then
这里我称为 np.linalg
we want the inverse of
然后得到它的倒数
that and then we're going to multiply that by the transpose and then the response.
然后我们把它乘以转置矩阵 然后乘以反应
Perfect. So, now you can see that
非常好 这时你会发现
our intercept value matches here and then the slope attached
截距值匹配这里 然后这个斜率
to the number of bathrooms and then the slope attached to the number of
与卫生间数量相关 这个斜率与
bedrooms matches and then again the slope attached to the area matches.
卧室数量相关 这个斜率与建筑面积相关
Because libraries like stats models exist,
因为存在 statsmodels 这种库
we don't need to perform the operations in this way.
我们不需这样进行运算
However, having an understanding of
然而理解
the optimization techniques can help you
最优化技巧可以帮助你了解
understand why certain operations might not work.
为什么有些运算不能起作用
In the next optional section,
在接下来的的部分中
we will see an example where understanding
我们将会看到
this equation is helpful for understanding our results.
理解这个方程式有利于理解结果的例子